https://deliverthedream.org/privacy-policy

Programs
Beach Bash (Virtual)
Campfire Series (Virtual)
Canvas & Connections (Virtual)
Family Fishing Day (Virtual)
Family Fun Days
Garden Party (Virtual)
HOPE at home (Virtual)
Sports Spectacular (Virtual)
Important Privacy Notice
This notice is being provided on behalf of Deliver the Dream, Inc., a not-for-profit organization (collectively referred to as the “Deliver the Dream").
We value your privacy and, as required by law, the following describes important information regarding how we collect public and nonpublic personal information, how the information is disclosed, and your rights. Please review this information carefully.
Information We May Collect
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications or other forms;
Information provided by you on our website(s);
Information provided by you such as credit card information to verify your name, address, and other information, as well as to bill you for approved donations; and
Information We May Disclose And To Whom
We only disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law. Nonaffiliated third parties are companies not under common control or ownership of the Deliver the Dream. For example, information may be provided to government entities in response to subpoenas. It may also be shared as part of the donation and/or volunteer process. You may not opt-out of us sharing this type of information.
We may also disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing arrangements. You may not opt-out of us sharing this type of information with these types of nonaffiliated third parties. As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party.
Information Security
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those individuals who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.
Changes To The Policy
We reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy. If material changes are made, we will provide a revised policy to all current customers.
Footer Menu
Home
About Us
Volunteer
Events
Blog
Contact Us
Latest Posts
Sep 06, 2020
Wouldn’t this Be a Great Time for a Scavenger Hunt?
Aug 18, 2020
Contact Us
SEOSEOmarketing digitalDrone ServicesDrone Roof Inspectiondumpster rentalDumpster Rental Myrtle BeachSEO AgencySpa ManagementChicago SpaBanner PrintingGuide RodsCredit Card ProcessingTeste CS 48Hair SalonAuto InsuranceCharlotte ElectricianCeratoneCirurgia de CatarataCirurgia de CatarataCeratoconeGranite CountertopsGranite CountertopsHome RemodelingParkland MagazineHouse CleaningeCommerce Optimization SoftwareSEO company Myrtle BeachSEO companySEOSail Boat RentalsMarine ContractingSEO CompanyADHD Testlimo servicedog trainingPalm Beach RoofingPrivate InvestigatorOrganic Skin CareMattress Atlantainterior decoratorasheville spabusiness cardslos angeles spaskids bikinisHastens MattressSell BusinessImpact WindowsGarmin GPSWall StreetMold Testingreal estatesecurity companycleveland roofingMansions UKOrlando SpaAdhd Doctorcreate decalInterior DesignSugar ScrubWindow TintingValencia HomesFinancial NewsTeste CSreclaimed woodChattanooga SpaAir Condition RepairBoca Raton Real Estatemegasporebioticmiami printer repairelectricianpublic adjustersprinter leasingsecurityboca bayoudesigner lightingroofing companycoral springs dentistVideo Production Orlandobrighton sandalnonprofit charitycustom suitsboynton beach dentisthemp oilboat rentalmattress ashevilleCPA Tampawater fastingLife MentoringPaintball NYC4500 nitroairboat rides airboat toursairboat tourBoca Raton Pawncateringairboat evergladesbradenton Dentalair boatingmiami boat detailingglass railingsdiscount dealsN95 Particulate RespiratorMold RemediationChristian Musicbradenton dentistInterior Designchicken cagesIT SpecialistImpact Windowseye corrector serumcateringmarlin fishinglife coachimpact windowsinterior designerworkers comp lawyersommoreair purifiershomecaremanufacturingelectricianremodelingmiadermfotógrafoproperty managementwaterfront propertiesair purifiers
Copyright © 2020 Deliver the Dream, Inc., All Rights Reserved. | Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions | SEO James Florida SEO Company
×
Make a Donation
Donation Amount
$10
$25
$50
$100
$150
$200
Billing Information
Donate Now
Online Payment Information
Want to stay up-to-date with Deliver the Dream's News, Retreats and Events?
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTRead MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
